Guide to the Cornell University Department of Mathematics records, 1877-1976.
Department of Mathematics records, 1877-1976.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Department of Mathematics records, 1877-1976.
14-19-2216
Cornell University. Department of Mathematics.
8.8 cubic ft.
Term reports, student lists, correspondence, teaching schedules, minutes, papers, scrapbooks, a textbook, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Bound term reports and student lists, 1890-1976, with some correspondence (lists were computer-generated after 1956); teaching schedules, 1910-1975; Mathematical Club records including minutes and papers presented, 3 volumes, 1891-1901; Mathematical Department Scrapbooks of examinations, 1877-1893; and Differential and Integral Calculus, by Virgil Snyder and John Irwin Hutchinson, with a syllabus and a list of other titles in the Modern Mathematical Series, including ones by other Cornell professors.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Bound term reports and student lists, 1890-1976, with some correspondence (lists were computer-generated after 1956); teaching schedules, 1910-1975; Mathematical Club records including minutes and papers presented, 3 volumes, 1891-1901; Mathematical Department Scrapbooks of examinations, 1877-1893; and Differential and Integral Calculus, by Virgil Snyder and John Irwin Hutchinson, with a syllabus and a list of other titles in the Modern Mathematical Series, including ones by other Cornell professors.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Department of Mathematics.
Subjects:
Mathematics--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Examination reports, 1890-1896 (Box 1)
- Examination reports, 1897-1902 (Box 1)
- Examination reports, 1902-1908 (Box 1)
- Examination reports, 1908-1913 (Box 1)
- Examination reports, 1911-1916 (Box 1)
- Examination reports, 1916-1920 (Box 1)
- Term reports, 1920-1923 (Box 2)
- Term reports, 1924-1926 (Box 2)
- Term reports, 1927-1929 (Box 2)
- Term reports, 1929-1932 (Box 2)
- Term reports, 1932-1935 (Box 2)
- Term reports, 1935-1939 (Box 2)
- Term reports, 1939-1942 (Box 2)
- Student lists, 1918-1923 (Box 3)
- Student lists, 1923-1927 (Box 3)
- Student lists, 1928-1933 (Box 3)
- Student lists, 1933-1940 (Box 3)
- Student lists, 1940-1943 (Box 3)
- Student lists, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
- Student lists, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
- Term reports, 1942-1944 (Box 4)
- Term reports, 1944-1946 (Box 4)
- Term reports, 1946-1948 (Box 4)
- Term reports, 1948-1950 (Box 4)
- Term reports, 1950-1953 (Box 4)
- Term reports, 1953-1956 (Box 4)
- Term reports, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- Term reports, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Student lists, 1945-1947 (Box 5)
- Student lists, 1947-1950 (Box 5)
- Student lists, 1950-1953 (Box 5)
- Student lists, 1956-1958 (Box 5)
- Student lists, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
- Student lists, 1961-1963 (Box 5)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1956-1958 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1960-1961 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1961-1962 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1963-1964 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1963-1965 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1964-1965 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1965-1966 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1966 (Box 6)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1966-1967 (Box 7)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1967 (Box 7)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1967 (Box 7)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1968-1969 (Box 7)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1968-1969 (Box 7)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1969-1970 (Box 7)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1969-1971 (Box 7)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1970-1971 (Box 8)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1971-1973 (Box 8)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1972-1973 (Box 8)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1973-1974 (Box 8)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1975-1976 (Box 8)
- Computer-generated lists (by course, consolidated), 1975-1976 (Box 8)
- Teaching schedules, 1910-1927 (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1920s (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1930s (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1940s (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1950-1954 (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1955-1959 (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1960-1964 (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
- Teaching schedules, 1970s (Box 9)
- Minutes and papers presented
  - Mathematical Club, 1891-1894 (Box 9)
  - Mathematical Club Division B, 1891-1894 (Box 9)
  - Oliver Mathematical Club, 1898-1901 (Box 9)
- Mathematical Department scrapbooks - exams
  - No. 1, 1877-1887 (Box 10)
  - No. 3, 1891-1893 (Box 10)
- Mathematical Department scrapbooks, 1887-1891 (Box 11)